<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>React Native Offline First Library on </title>
    <link>https://angaza-elimu.github.io/offline/</link>
    <description>Recent content in React Native Offline First Library on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://angaza-elimu.github.io/offline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contribution Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://angaza-elimu.github.io/offline/contribution-guidelines/contribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angaza-elimu.github.io/offline/contribution-guidelines/contribution/</guid>
      <description>Describe the bug A clear and concise description of what the bug is.
Current Behavior
 What code are you running and what is happening? Include a screenshot if it makes sense.  Expected Behavior
 What do you expect should be happening?  How to reproduce  You must provide a way to reproduce the problem. Either re-create the bug on Snack or link to a GitHub repository with code that reproduces the bug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://angaza-elimu.github.io/offline/getting-started/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angaza-elimu.github.io/offline/getting-started/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>React Native Offline First Library This project is a library that implements an offline first approach with SQLite and React Native (featuring TypeScript and CocoaPods under the hood).The library stores requests to local memory in abscence of a connection and share These instructions only cover iOS usage at this time.
Install JS dependencies npm install offline-react-sync  Install iOS dependencies (requires Cocoapods) pushd ios/ pod install popd  Start the React Native Metro Bundler npm start  Compile TypeScript source in watch mode npm run tsc -- -w  Run the Jest tests in watch mode npm test  Open the source in VS Code code .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
